Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Dialogue adaptation & Timing by:Sparta
Baylin.
Mayfer & Sons Law Firm.
Baylin Bay.
Come on. let's get this over with!
Hit me as hard as you can. Muk.
Come on!
Come on. you're not getting out of it.
One. two. or three?
Wake up. Jared.
Muk. no matter what.
you're gonna lose again.
Easy.
One hit.
Send it towards the base.
Let's go!
I thought it was a cheeseburger.
Or your mom's ass.
I'll destroy you with this.
Okay. Allen.
Anyway. you delivered the Glenn Gary
lines perfectly.
One more word and I'll bring him back.
You're awesome.
You two talk way too much.
Finish him. Tyler.
Damn it! Shit!
Chef!
What are you doing?
I think I broke my arm.
Let me see. Let me see.
You got it. Joe.
Alright. kids.
Ice cream's on me.
Let's go.
You're seriously talking
about the Glenn Gary lines?
No. actually. you played
really well.
Even better than
Alec Baldwin.
Exactly.
Good job. son.
We suck.
Watch your mouth.
Anyway.
It's kinda weird that a dentist
is treating kids to ice cream.
You must be so pissed you
couldn't catch that ball.
At least this season there are no
more games for you to mess up for us.
Hank. what are you doing?
Nothing. He dropped it.
Apologize to him.
You played really well.
Now you're in trouble.
What are you doing. man?
Dad. Chai just came out.
He'll forget about it soon.
After he shoves your face
into the dirt?
Dad. look what I've got on me.
Oh my God. look how beautiful it is.
Here you go. sweetie.
The deadly sting. the locust.
and the mischievous goat.
It's kinda gross.
They don't look gross.
What's that about
the frog in the pond?
Probably a joke.
Let me try.
Sorry.
That's not yours.
Apologize to him.
Sorry.
I'm so sorry your son
is a little shit.
Leave him alone. Benji.
He'll get what he deserves.
That's how it always goes.
Thank you.
Isn't he sweet?
But. Jared...
You'd be an amazing player
if you were on another team.
You deserve it.
I don't know what to say. Never mind.
I will accept the ice cream
with great pride.
Eat your prize.
You'll be puking all night. Cam.
Come on.
Wanna come with us?
I'm free too. Lizzie.
And my car is available.
Hank. she's way out of your league.
Come on. Bye. Lizzie.
Bye. Lizzie.
What were you thinking?
I just wanted to see if I'm still
lactose intolerant.
I think mom and dad
made it all up.
Yeah. right. You have to live
with that lactose gas.
How is it?
It's good.
How was the game?
It was as good as my fart.
Any big plans for the summer?
Probably just the beach.
Probably doing another internship.
At a law firm.
My parents want me
to do my internship.
Typical parents.
Are you gonna charge them?
No. my mom gives me money.
Then give them my regards.
You rascal.
I took the bell down.
Don't throw coins.
I told you. there's no more bell.
There's been no bell
for years. goddamn it!
I put the bell up because I thought
it would be fun if someone hit it.
But those little bastards came and started
throwing coins like it was a carnival.
And I had to break my back
all day picking up those coins.
But you know what?
There's no more bell.
So get the hell out of here.
What about you. Jared?
Got anything planned?
Yeah. He's gonna work for me.
He's gonna make enough money
to buy a Ferrari.
I'll mow your lawn so you
can go to camp.
Why would I mow your lawn when
you could go to camp?
You'll need money in high school.
Chicks are expensive.
Trust me.
I was broke
when we were together.
That was before I became
an entrepreneur.
Are you gonna buy a lawnmower?
Exactly. Roger.
I need some motor oil
for the green machine.
And by green. I mean
the one that brings in the cash.
Sure thing.
Thanks. Roger.
Say hi to my folks.
I will.
Roger!
Wait up!
What's wrong with your sister?
She used to laugh at all my jokes.
You want her back?
Stop trying to be cool
and just act like a human being.
Did you take the bell down?
Why would you even set up a bell
for kids to throw coins at?
Today I only spent 57 cents.
And it only cost me three pieces of gum.
He's a psycho.
He probably has dead bodies
in his basement.
Tie your shoe. I did.
I need braces. They're so long.
Did you get it?
Get what?
I'll meet you at the car.
Are they gonna beat you up?
Oh my God. Go.
Are you smoking?
Let's go.
Bye. Jared.
Any fireworks left?
Just a few.
Cool. bring 'em.
I wanna film them.
That's the ice cream man's song.
Ring-a-ding-dong.
ring-a-ding-dong.
Ring-a-ding-ding. ring-a-ding-dong.
that's the ice cream man's song.
Hey. Hey.
Hello. Mrs. Anderson.
Elliot's not feeling well.
We were just chatting.
It came on all of a sudden.
Probably the heat.
Well. tell him to text me later
if he's feeling better and wants to hang.
I will.
Tell your mom
that Saturday is perfect.
Of course. Thanks. Mrs. Henderson.
You're welcome. sweetie.
Come on. Sebastian.
Elliot. your dark-haired friend.
is coming down with a baseball bat.
Fuck you.
Give me my bike back.
It's yours?
It's mine now.
Really?
Because if you steal it.
my dad is gonna sue you.
If you've got the balls.
come fight me for it.
But it's already mine.
Jared. what's going on?
Everything okay. honey?
Yeah. we're just messing around.
Yeah.
The bastard in here
is always joking.
Okay.
I can take this whenever I want.
This is gonna be a great summer.
What do you do? Aren't you bored
going to the beach every day?
Same thing every day.
No. I just...
I sunbathe.
hang out with my friends.
I'm having a good time.
Skye brought speakers. so...
She brought Tony Robbins
with you to the beach?
That's exactly what he means.
And James Carville?
Who?
Him?
I just remembered.
The speechwriter.
The one who wrote
Bill Clinton's speeches?
Awesome.
What your father wants to know is...
what's gonna help you
get into an Ivy League school.
Be a lifeguard?
Or do an internship
at a law firm?
With a 4.0 GPA.
Vacation is for spending time
with my friends.
If you don't have friends.
what's the point?
What your father is trying to say is...
your summer needs a plan.
Some structure.
I have a plan.
I go out. I sleep in.
I tan. and repeat.
Looks like you're already
a lawyer.
No need for law school.
Done.
Just because Grandpa wasn't the first
in the family. doesn't mean
I have to be the first either.
Someone has to break
the family curse.
You know. if Grandpa were alive.
he'd be looking at your hands
and feet before you.
Actually. if Grandpa were alive.
he'd have her locked up
for disobeying her parents.
That's right. I'm tired of
using my brain.
I'm gonna cash in on my hotness
while I'm still young.
Start an OnlyFans.
How do you even know what that is?
Ugh. gross.
Even as a joke.
Why are you playing such an old song?
Mom heard it this morning
and it reminded me of when
you were sweet...
and you were always
all over me.
That was when I was six.
That's so embarrassing.
It's a mom's job
to embarrass her kids.
You succeeded.
Guys. did you see that weird
ice cream truck?
What's weird about it?
I don't know.
It showed up like it was following me
on purpose. I don't know.
I feel sorry for whoever
kidnaps Jared.
Elizabeth. don't.
Take it back.
You'd be the perfect kidnap victim.
That's not great either.
but at least it's a positive.
Wait. What's weird about it?
Probably just the music it plays.
I don't know.
It's weird.
Dad didn't see him at the club.
So...
Mom. are you gonna need
the car tomorrow?
No. probably not. Why?
It's skip day.
Skipping school.
That's what some people call it.
But it's more like a field trip.
That's what everyone calls it.
I heard that Jesse's brother...
is skipping with his friends.
He won't stop talking about it.
I figured we could just go first
and ask for forgiveness later.
Jared. shut up.
That's what makes it so fucking funny. right?
Shut up. It's a tradition
for the juniors...
to spend the last week
with the outgoing seniors.
It's a tradition. It's fun.
Why didn't we have
that tradition...
So you're telling me that this week
you're all gonna skip school?
Pretty much.
You'll be under
double surveillance.
I'm going. To school.
To the water park.
In your dreams.
Finals are over.
School ends on Wednesday.
No big deal.
Go on Thursday.
Then it's not skipping.
That's exactly the point.
You're supposed to break the rules.
That's the whole reason
rules exist.
Dad's just playing
the lawyer now. isn't he?
Dad's defending
the accused.
They didn't do anything wrong.
If they didn't do anything wrong.
then fine.
Honey. mom can give you
the car.
But either way.
you're not going.
Someone has to stay
with Jared.
No. I can stay.
I can't believe this.
If something happens.
he can stay at Elliot's.
Which it won't.
Exactly.
As much as we trust
both of you...
we can't leave
two kids alone.
Accidents can happen.
We want an adult
to be there.
And in this case.
that adult is you. Okay?
Either way...
you have to go to skip day.
Find someone to stay with you.
Otherwise I'm taking you with me.
No. don't take me to the water park.
It's full of girls in bikinis.
Shut up. Jared.
It's no place for a pre-teen like me.
You're so annoying.
You're not taking me either.
Yeah.
Take you where?
I'll take you to school tomorrow.
I'd love to see Dad
go to school
and talk about Mitt Romney.
Mitt Romney.
Why. sweetie?
Do we have Mitt Romney
for dessert. ice cream?
Piper.
Honey. what's wrong?
Do you have more ice cream?
Fran!
What's going on?
Oh my God!
Brett!
Watch out. kids.
Sweetie. what's wrong?
My necklace.
I dropped it.
We'll find it tomorrow.
Go to bed.
But I can't sleep
without it.
Please. Daddy.
Okay.
Sweetie.
Are you sure?
I don't see anything.
What's that?
Is that oil?
Sebastian?
Our kids have completely
lost their minds.
Steve.
Honey.
I have a gun.
I'll shoot.
Elliot!
Honey. what are you doing?
What did you do to Dad?
Fuck. what is that?
Elliot!
What are you doing?
Elliot. put it down.
Elliot!
Enough. come to Mom.
Come to Mom right now.
No!
What are you doing?
Put it down.
No. no. no. honey!
No. don't do it!
No. no. no!
Come to Mom. please.
Mom loves you.
No! No!
Come here. sweetie. Come on.
Good job. baby.
Oh my God!
Are you okay?
What happened?
Someone hurt my mom.
Who?
Me.
What's going on?
The Farbers left
the door open.
Probably getting ready to leave.
Should I go close it?
No. they'll figure it out.
Better text Fran
just in case.
What?
Why is there
an ice cream truck here?
I heard Lizzie and Skye
making a big fuss.
After they found out
they're not going to skip day.
That guy gives me
the creeps.
Damn it.
I thought we were doing
ice cream puns.
Which is a little weird.
Probably nothing.
I'll call security
to come take a look.
Watch out.
Your mom left this here.
Muk.
Brett.
You're sick. aren't you?
See you at school. I guess.
She's acting really weird.
What the hell...
Elliot. Elliot!
Damn it.
Oh my God. Marcella!
So. I edited the video.
and I thought we could
do a little...
Okay.
What's this? Are we having a contest
for who can dress like a zombie in pajamas?
Good morning. Mr. Mayfer.
Any sign of your friend
Mr. Henderson?
I saw him a little while ago.
He's a mess.
He said he was going
to the nurse's office.
Yeah.
The terrible illness
called summer.
It strikes around the end
of every school year.
Want me to go check?
Yes. but come back quick.
Because there's only
a few days left.
So we still have
three days of school.
Let's continue
with fractions and mixed numbers.
Who can break down
72 into prime factors?
Are you okay?
Stop asking me that.
How does it look to you?
Sorry. I just...
Is it just me or is something
weird going on?
You shouldn't be skipping class.
It's my responsibility.
Everything's normal.
Yeah.
For Tommy.
Elliot?
Did you see Elliot?
Guys.
I thought someone was outside.
Do we have a test today or what?
Mr. B. you can't give us
a test
on the last week
of school.
At least now I know
it's not a joke.
What joke?
Ask your friends.
Someone told them it's silent day
or some new holiday they invented.
Hey. guys!
Greg is sick
and won't talk.
Watch your language. Mr. Green.
Language.
I'm the only one talking.
Don't you think that's weird?
I thought everyone had left
for vacation.
But since you're here...
take out the microscope.
What do you mean she didn't show up?
Mr. Hamlin...
Should we go check her house?
Mr. Hamlin!
You don't understand.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
Hello?
Class isn't over yet.
I don't know.
Sorry.
Where are you going?
Are you skipping?
Sorry. no. Where are you going?
No. class
isn't over yet.
Tommy. get back here right now!
Okay. okay.
I'll deal with Tommy
and the others later.
Now. all of you.
back to your seats.
Sit down.
Marcella.
Elliot.
Elliot. this isn't funny.
Frank. what's going on?
The whole school is filled
with ice cream fudge.
Ready? Let's go.
Ice cream break!
This is not a fire drill!
Back to class. now!
What the hell is going on here?
Must be a prank.
There's gotta be
a camera somewhere.
We know you're filming us.
Yeah.
Elliot!
Come on.
Elliot. please!
Elliot. don't think about it
Get out.
Jared!
The smell...
Cover your nose.
Move aside.
I want to get through.
Show some respect.
What flavor is it?
That much?
Give yours to me.
Okay. fine.
No.
Oh my God! Oh my God!
Kids. don't look!
Someone get a doctor!
Don't laugh...
It's not funny at all.
Damn it!
What the hell is going on?
Back off! That's enough!
I said back off!
Oh my God!
My boy... Oh my God!
911. how can I help you?
Yes. sir.
My name is Bob Maloney.
from Meadowbrook.
Please come quickly!
I'm not sure if the kid jumped
or if it was an accident. but it looks like...
Yes. sir.
And then there was a brick...
What?
Damn it. the bike is lost.
What happened here?
What's going on? Come in!
Oh my God.
Now let's look at
the housefly.
It might seem like
a completely ordinary insect.
but if you look at it closely.
you'll see that it has
the same characteristics.
Let's go find ours.
This room is usually
always quiet
What are you doing?
Let me go!
What are you gonna do to me?
Get in.
No way!
Oh my God!
Is this really happening?
I know.
What the hell?
Oh my God!
Okay. Manny.
Come on. hurry up!
Marcella!
Come here!
Mia. it's me.
Where's Tommy?
He's at the back exit.
Help! Help!
What's that?
What the hell is that?
Sting! Let's go!
Here! Come here!
Here! Come on. come on!
Tommy. get in! Close the door!
What the hell is going on?
Something bad.
Someone bad.
The ice cream man.
The police are coming!
Back off!
Back off. kids!
I need everyone to back off. please.
Back! Hurry. back!
Oh my God.
What are you doing?
Ring-a-ding-ding...
That's the ice cream man's song.
Why are you singing?
Stop singing. now!
Stop it right now!
It's not funny.
Shit!
They threw glue in his face!
We need to find a phone.
Hold on. I've got one.
What? That's the top model!
It's like an iPhone.
You know more people
use Android.
Just make the call!
- We didn't say anything
- Yeah. talk to yourself
I'm watching you
out of the corner of my eye.
This is the number
for Martin Mayfer's office.
Leave a message.
I'll try calling Mom.
Sorry. how does this work?
Shit!
The fire department is here.
Where is it? Where are you?
Here! Help us!
Look over there!
Don't come closer. kid!
Back off.
Hang in there.
I'm here.
Step back.
Hey. hey.
No. wait!
He's here.
Everyone. follow him.
We need to move fast.
I don't know. but we can't
stay here.
Oh my God!
They don't want to kill us.
They want to take us...
Oh my God!
Is this for real?
What's that sound?
What the hell?
What's that?
Damn it!
What the hell is that?
The ice cream is possessed!
Did you eat it?
What? No. I'm lactose intolerant.
Probably more than
you want to know. but...
Hold on. sorry.
What do you mean possessed?
It turns you into a demon.
Did you eat it?
Did you eat it or not?
I threw it up. I'm fine.
So can we trust her?
I saw her throw up.
Okay.
Hold on.
Were you watching me?
No. no... Okay. yes. a little.
But not in a creepy way.
I just happened to see you.
Jared. it's okay.
I got it all out.
Okay. I'll keep an eye on you.
Okay. what do you say?
Help us figure out a way
out of here.
Hold on. Lizzie.
Help! Someone. help me!
What the hell is going on?
Siri!
Call Mom and Dad.
This is Martin Mayfer's office.
Leave a message
and we'll get back to you.
Siri!
Call that idiot!
Turn off the sound. man!
Shut up. it's Lizzie.
Lizzie. I'm losing my mind!
The kids are killing everyone!
You need to get here. now!
I can't move my arm at all.
Call an ambulance!
What? Call
Mom or Dad.
No. let's call a doctor.
I already tried calling them.
but I got voicemail.
Wait. did you have ice cream?
What?
Last night.
Skye and I had some.
Jared. this is an emergency!
It's poisoned.
It's possessed.
You need to get it out
of your system.
You need to throw up.
I told you I can't
move my arms!
I'm paralyzed
all over my body.
It might cause
paralysis in teenagers.
Or it could make them
pass out.
You need to throw up.
I said use a toothbrush.
I heard her.
Jared.
You need to get out of there.
I know. We're praying
they don't find us.
If we go to church...
The demonic creature
can't go in there.
To the church.
No one's ever gone down
to the basement.
If you can get there.
I can come pick you up.
The church.
Shit!
We're screwed.
Let's go. let's go!
Let's go!
Don't be a chicken. do it!
Do it!
You can do it!
Damn it!
Get away from there.
What the hell is that?
Tell them to be quiet.
Hello?
Mrs. Poole?
Penelope. what are you doing?
We need to get out of here.
Come on.
Penelope!
Skye. Skye!
Skye. wake up. hurry!
I knew you'd understand.
New phone? Who is it?
Chris. stop messing around.
Help us.
The kids have gone crazy.
They attacked people.
What are you talking about?
Shit!
Wen. this way!
It can get in now!
Try that.
Yeah. use it! Yes. yes!
Why is it so heavy?
Spray them!
Hurry!
First. take out the pin.
Take out the pin!
What are you doing?
Hurry. take out the pin!
Want me to help you?
Okay.
Now that it's ready.
spray them!
Let's go!
Oh my God!
We did it!
Let's go. let's go!
Get inside. quick!
Damn it. it's locked!
What are you doing?
I'm trying!
The door is locked!
Jessie! Jessie!
We can't make it! Let's go!
Hurry. let's go!
Break it!
Damn it! I'm losing my mind!
Damn it!
Everyone!
What's that?
Close the door. quick!
I'll lock the door.
We're trapped.
The outside door.
There! There's one there too.
Go. go. go.
We won't leave
anyone behind.
We won't...
The other side of the fence
leads to the church.
We just need to get
to that patrol car.
Damn it. Jared. hurry!
Forget it. it's okay.
Come on. hurry!
What are you waiting for?
Take it. I don't want it back.
Oh my God...
What's that?
Hurry. they'll kill us.
What a mess.
Come on!
I'm telling you. I'm a genius.
This hand is like magic.
No.
I'm not...
Good. right?
Don't look back.
Run. hurry!
Sorry.
What the hell is that?
I'm losing my mind.
Keep going. let's go!
Okay. that way.
Wait for them to leave first.
But there's too many.
But it's the shortest way.
I don't know... it looks
like suicide.
Better find
another way.
We absolutely have
to get to the church.
Mia! Oh my God!
Sebastian. are you okay?
I'm fine.
Mia. are you okay?
Thanks. No problem.
How did you know to do that?
I'm twelve years old.
I already know how to make
myself throw up.
That's dark. I like it.
We need to get to the church.
Let's go. let's go.
I'm losing it.
What the hell?
Pass the rope. pass it.
One single rope. weave it tight.
Hold on tight. don't let go.
Let's go. let's go.
Get up. hurry.
I'm stuck!
Hurry. hurry!
Don't let it
take over me.
Idiot!
I'll beat you black and blue!
Run! Run!
Hey. you useless piece of shit!
This way!
Okay.
Guys...
What?
Why does the church
have a freezer like that?
Probably where they keep
the bodies.
What bodies?
For funerals.
The ice cream...
It's in there.
Not in the truck?
Maybe they have
a bigger plan.
There it is!
Oh hell.
Damn it! They're all in here.
I told you.
Let's defrost it.
Find the plug or the switch.
Oh my God!
Yes. oh my God!
The switch is right next to him.
Save yourselves!
Leave!
He's telling us to leave!
No way.
the ice cream man is there!
The door!
Damn it. no!
We're screwed.
We're gonna die in here.
At least
we're going to Heaven.
Tommy. your joke
is not helping.
I wasn't joking.
There's no signal at all.
But Lizzie said
she's coming here. so...
Good thing we're
in the freezer.
That's the first place
everyone will look. Jared.
Want me to get you down?
Chris.
Help me down.
So now you finally agree
to be with me?
Very funny.
Get me down. hurry.
First promise me
you won't be a dick.
Seriously?
We're gonna do this now?
No better time.
Okay. Chris. I...
I promise I won't do
anything stupid.
And if you help me down.
I might consider going
to dinner with you.
Assuming there's
any restaurant left.
But first. can you
help me get down?
Dinner or a movie?
Dinner.
Okay. deal.
Help me.
I accept your terms.
Quick. jump!
Nice car.
So you really are
the boss now?
I told you.
but you didn't believe me.
Now I can even take you
to the movies.
Where are we going?
The church.
Jared is hiding there.
Okay. let's go.
It's my fault.
All of it.
How?
I know who the ice cream man is.
You could say
I created him.
What?
Why did you create him. Father?
I was part of the reason
all this happened.
Who is the ice cream man?
His name was Jonathan Smiley.
He drove an ice cream truck.
No one knew his name
or his past.
But he spoke with
a foreign accent.
So we thought he was
a refugee from some war zone.
All he wanted was to make
kids happy
with his ice cream.
Kids trust adults
way too much.
Especially adults who
are in positions of trust.
Who wear uniforms.
Teachers.
Religious figures.
But some of those adults
thought they could take advantage
of that trust.
What did the ice cream man do?
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
But he paid the price
for someone else's crimes.
Crimes that were horrific
and unforgivable.
I was a young priest.
I tried to speak out.
but the powerful
forced me to stay silent.
The scandal was too big.
Rumors spread
through the small town.
Something had to be done.
So they decided
to put the blame
on someone
they could get rid of.
The ice cream man.
There was a lawyer
who went after him.
He made the kids
testify in court.
All the kids testified
that the ice cream man was guilty.
The adults put lies
in the kids' mouths
and taught them
to repeat them
when they testified.
What was the lawyer's name?
There's a special place
in hell
for people like
Milton Mayfer.
He's my grandfather.
Hold on.
You still haven't told us
how he was able to do this.
When he was in prison.
someone went to visit him.
He said he was a lawyer.
but every word he said
was a lie.
Except for one promise.
That he would help the ice cream man
get his revenge on the town.
He was a necromancer.
Someone who could
raise the dead
in exchange for money.
The ice cream man sold his soul
in exchange for revenge.
The magician promised him
that he would give him
supernatural powers
when those kids
became adults.
Welcome to
Baylin Bay
population 7.381.
When the town had long forgotten what it did.
The ice cream man would return
to remind them.
The next day. he was found
dead in his cell.
They buried him in an unmarked grave.
by the riverbank.
To resurrect him.
the necromancer took his place.
He's lying there now.
How do we stop
the ice cream man?
If we ever get out of here.
Kill the necromancer.
The ice cream man dies
with him.
So all we have to do
is kill the necromancer?
Yes. but he's not alone.
He lies with a siren.
who will alert him
if anyone attacks.
So we have to kill
the siren too
and then kill
the necromancer.
Just killing him isn't enough.
You have to cut his head off.
Okay. So we kill
the siren
and then cut his head off.
Okay.
But you must not look at him.
The magician can still
seduce people.
even after his head
is cut off.
Hold on. We have to kill
the siren
and then cut off
the necromancer's head.
But we can't even
look at him?
Wait. This is way too complicated.
How are we supposed to kill him
if we can't...
You kill the siren.
Cut off the necromancer's head.
He'll be wearing
a ceremonial hood.
Do not remove
the hood from his head.
Find the ice cream man.
Take the hood off
his head.
Make the ice cream man look
the necromancer in the eyes.
And he will die.
Wait. and the kids?
Will they die?
The cursed children
will sleep.
And when they wake up.
they won't remember a thing.
Quick. hide.
I'll distract the ice cream man
when he comes in.
You lock the door.
This is how I'll atone.
by saving all three of you.
Go hide.
Behold the Cross of the Lord.
Let the forces of evil
be dissolved.
The Lion of Judah.
the Root of David has conquered.
Alleluia. Alleluia.
Alleluia.
Run! This way!
Damn it. run! This way!
Hurry!
Where did everyone go?
Jared. Lizzie.
I told you he'd come back
to apologize.
Seriously?
Damn it.
Looks like he rang
Roger's bell.
He's the one who hung it.
Chris.
Did you manage to reach
our parents?
I left a message.
The office answering machine picked up.
Then we...
Let's get the hell out of here
and call them on the way.
We're going to the cemetery.
Yeah. we'll all end up buried there
if we don't get out of here fast.
Let's go. We know how to stop him.
We just need to...
Wait. Where's Tommy?
Tommy. Tommy!
Come help us carry this stuff.
What are you doing. going gold
prospecting like an old west cowboy?
If you want to dig up a grave
with your bare hands. go ahead.
So we're going to dig up
the grave.
Where did everyone go?
The adults are all dead.
The teenagers who ate the ice cream
have fallen into a coma.
And the kids have disappeared.
Father. did he tell you
why the ice cream man is doing this?
Yes. It has to do
with our grandfather. Milton.
He made the kids testify
in court and they blamed him.
He probably came back
for revenge.
My mom and dad
testified too.
I told you being a lawyer
is a family curse.
Chris.
Looks like she needs help.
I killed my...
Are you okay?
Chris. get out of here. quick!
I killed him. Chris. go!
I'm so sorry.
How are we gonna find him now?
It's an unmarked grave.
There are thousands of them.
Hold on.
He said it's by the river. right?
There are maples
on the banks.
They have a lot of sap.
They're a pain
to trim.
They've ruined
all my chainsaws.
What?
I take back everything I said
about you being an idiot.
Have you ever said that?
Millions of times.
Never to your face.
I think the word
you used is retarded.
Guys. can we look for maples
by the river?
There!
Chris!
Better back off.
No turning back now.
We're surrounded.
I figured that out too.
They're getting closer.
What do we do?
Press it!
Damn it!
Trust me.
We're screwed!
Stop the car.
quick!
Okay. okay.
Find the grave.
I'll distract them.
Chris. I want to...
Go! Help the others.
Don't forget. maples
by the river.
The one that has sap.
You're awesome.
Good luck.
Damn it.
What are you doing?
I found it!
That tree?
Probably this one.
Not the time
for guessing wrong.
No grass.
Definitely this one.
What the hell?
Damn it!
What the hell is that?
Get out of my car!
Oh my God!
It's all dirty!
Damn it.
I just had it washed!
You little shit!
Oh my God!
Okay.
I'll do it.
No.
My family started this.
We're going to end it.
Guys. help out.
I'll count to three.
One. two...
Hold on.
It's a trap.
Elliot!
What's happening?
The magic is wearing off.
Some of his ice cream flavors
don't work.
He set a trap for you.
Don't listen to him.
that's not Elliot.
No. it's me!
Everything that comes out
of that necromancer's mouth is a lie.
Don't trust him.
Jared. it's dangerous.
Lizzie. make him listen.
If we run. where are we going?
We're getting out of here.
I know.
But how?
Trust me.
You need to come with me.
Before he comes back.
I'll go.
If you tell me one thing.
Anything.
Come on.
What did you call me yesterday?
When I caught the ball
and won.
I called you a retard.
I made the team lose. Elliot.
Just like you messed up now.
Don't come near him.
I don't have to.
Mia.
Chris. help us!
Dig! Come on. hurry!
Shit!
Lizzie. give me the lighter.
Let's do this.
Alright. kid.
Time to have some fun.
Chris!
Kill him. quick!
Damn it!
It's delicious. Tommy.
Try it.
Mia. no!
Why not?
Adults can't be trusted.
He's right about that.
He's the only one
protecting us.
He gives us powers.
Powers to fight them.
He's so sweet. Tommy.
He loves us.
Offices - Beacon Street!
Jerry.
Don't look.
I'll kill Bayle.
Don't do it!
Why?
Tommy. don't look
no matter what!
I'm sorry. Tommy.
Every word he said
was a lie.
Except for one promise.
The ice cream man sold his soul
in exchange for revenge.
Ring-a-ding-ding. ring-a-ding-dong.
That's the ice cream song!
The end.
Dialogue adaptation & Timing by:Sparta
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm